https://prospect.org/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which The American Prospect collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the https://prospect.org website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by The American Prospect.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users’ means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the internet service providers used, and other similar information.
How we use collected information
We collect and use Users’ personal information for the following purposes:
To personalize user experience
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our Site
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from Users.
To improve customer service
Users’ information helps us to more effectively respond to customer service requests and support needs.
To process transactions
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order.
To send periodic emails
The email address Users provide for order processing may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If a User decides to opt in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, and reminders for subscription renewal. When a User subscribes, we may also use that information to contact them about new products or upcoming events, or to send them donation appeals or sponsored messages with offers from other organizations. In addition, we may share Users’ information with reputable companies who may contact them via mail or email with products or services we think will be of interest to them.
If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How we protect Users’ information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices, and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of Users’ personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that links to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to, or from, our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.
Advertising and web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance Users’ experience. The User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. The User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert them when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners. Both The American Prospect and our partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize a User’s computer each time the server sends the User an online advertisement to compile non-personal identification information about the User or others who use the User’s computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to the User. Users can visit Google.com/settings/ads to opt out of Google’s use of cookies. Users can also visit NetworkAdvertising.org/choices to opt out of other third parties’ use of cookies. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Changes to this privacy policy
We have the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Users acknowledge and agree that it is their responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact us.
This document was last updated in April 2019.
Copyright 2020 | The American Prospect, Inc. | All Rights Reserved
Built with Metro Publisher™
